Guide to the Records of the Office of Research Services/Office of Sponsored Programs RG.9.4
New York University Archives
- Research Administration
  - Sponsored Programs, Office of, 1981-1985 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Sponsored Programs, Office of, 1985-1991 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Sponsored Programs, Office of, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Sponsored Programs, Office of, 1994-1997 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Sponsored Progarms, Office of, Research Management Improvement (National Science Foundation Grant nm44242), 1974-1977 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Sponsored Programs, Office of, Research Management Improvment (National Science Foundation Grant nm44242), 1974-1977 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Sponsored Programs, Office of, Research Management Imporvement (National Science Foundation Grant nm44242), 1974-1977 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Sponsored Programs, Office of, Intramural memoranda and minutes, 1974-1977 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Sponsored Programs, Office of, Intramural memoranda and minutes, 1974-1977 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Sponsored Programs, Office of, Intramural memoranda and minutes, 1974-1977 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Sponsored Programs, Office of, Extramural Correspondence, 1974-1983 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Budget, Estimates, misc, 1975-1980 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Compliments, 1978-1996 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Cooper & Lybrand Study, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Cornell/NSF Town Meeting, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Development of Data Analysis, 1983-1985 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Freedom of Information Requests, 1981-1990 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Sponsored Programs and Operations, General University Certifications, 1990-1997 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Guide to Service, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Log, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Log, 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Log, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Log, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations Manuals, misc, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Memoranda & Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Memoranda, & Correspondence, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Memoranda & Correspondence, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Memoranda & Correspondence, 1962-1965 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Sponsored Programs, Operations, Memoranda, & Operations, 1968-1971 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Memoranda, & Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Memoranda, & Correspondences, 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Memoranda, & Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, newsletters, 1979-1984 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, NYU Annual Report (Five year Retrospective), 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Program Announcements, 1972-1997 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Research Recognition Award Proposal, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Signature Authority, 1971-2005 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Staffing and Budgets, 1973-1989 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Senior Staff Activates, 1986-1997 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Senior Staff Activates meeting agendas and minutes, 1993-1997 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Sponsored Research and Training Programs Manual, 1956-1967 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Sponsored Research and Traning Programs Manual, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Sponsored Research and Training Programs Manual, 1974-1977 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Sponsored Research and Training Program Manual, 1978-1986 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Sponsored Programs Operations, Sponsored Research and Training Program Manual, 1991-1997 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Research Administration, Related University Units
  - Academic Affairs, Office of, 1982-1990 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Academic Affairs, Office of, Ethics and Moral Value, 1978-1982 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Services, Equipment and Policy and Property Management, 1979-1998 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Development Office, 1958-1968 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Development Office, 1975-1982 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Development Office, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Development Office, 1983-1985 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Development Office, 1985-1991 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Development Office, 1991-1993 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Development Office, 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Finance Office, Contract Officer, 1966-1981 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Finance Office, Contract Officer, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Finance Office, Contract Officer, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Finance Office, Contract Officer, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Finance Office, Contract Officer, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Finance Office, Contract Officer, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Finance Office, Contract Officer, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Finance Office, Contract Officer, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Finance Office, Contract Officer, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Finance Office, Contract Officer, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Finance Office, Contract Officer, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Finance Office, Contract Officer, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Finance Office, Contract Officer, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Finance Office, Contract Officer, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Finance Office, Contract Officer, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Finance Office, Indirect Cost Agreements, 1963-1995 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Finance Office, Indirect Cost Policy, Privately Sponsored Programs, 1985-1993 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Finance Office, Sponsored Research Accounting, 1974-1985 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Finance Office, Sponsored Research Accounting, 1986-1989 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Finance Office, Sponsored Research Accounting, 1989-1991 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Finance Office, Sponsored Research Accounting, 1991-1993 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Finance Office, Sponsored Research Accounting, 1993-1996 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Personnel Matters, Code 103, 1981-1996 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Personnel Matters, Tax Cases, 1958-1983 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Personnel Matters, Tax Cases, 1986-1988 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Schools/Units
  - Graduate School Arts and Science, 1957-1966 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Graduate School Arts and Science, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Graduate School Arts and Science, 1968-1972 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, 1983-1986 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, 1986-1989 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, 1994-1998 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Deans' Correspondence and Memoranda, 1978-1991 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Dean of Science, 1989-1992 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Dean of Science, 1992-1995 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Neural Science, Center for, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Neural Science, Center for, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, New York State Center for Neural Science at New York University, 1987-1989 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, New York State Center for Neural Science at New York University (1 of 2), 1989 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, New York State Center for Neural Science at New York University (2 of 2), 1989 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, New York State Center for Neural Science at New York University, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Research Awards and Gifts, 1981-1983 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Technology Transfer Fund, 1990-1995 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Anthropology Department, 1968-1996 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Biology Department, 1959-1983 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Biology Department, Goldfeder Laboratory, 1973-1993 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Economics Department, 1969-1980 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Linguistics Department, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Politics Department, 1983-1993 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Psychology Department (including Neural Science Center), 1980-1988 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Sociology Department, 1970-1993 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Applied Science, 1974-1989 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Applied Science, Kinetic Hydro Engergy Conversion Study, 1984-1988 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Westbury Facility, 1984-1989 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, 1961-1983 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Courant Insitute of Mathematical Sciences, 1983-1986 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, 1986-1997 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science, Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, Center for Advanced Technology, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration, 1979-1997 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Continuing Education, School of, 1966-1968 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - College of Dentistry, 1968-1997 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - School of Education, 1959-1965 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - School of Education, 1965-1968 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - School of Education, 1968-1971 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - School of Education, 1979-1985 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - School of Education, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - School of Education, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - School of Education, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - School of Education, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - School of Education, 1989-1992 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - School of Education, 1992-1997 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - School of Engineering, 1965-1968 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - School of Engineering, 1969-1974 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - School of Law, 1988-1992 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - School of Medicine, Medical Center, 1962-1967 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - School of Medicine, Medical Center, 1968-1977 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - School of Medicine, Medical Center, 1982-1987 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - School of Medicine, Medical Center, 1987-1992 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - School of Medicine, Medical Center, 1992-1994 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - School of Medicine, Medical Center, 1994-1996 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Graduate School of Public Administration, 1971-1992 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Graduate School of Social Work, 1967-1988 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Tisch School of the Arts, 1967-1982 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Center for International Studies, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Center for International Studies, 1966-1973 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Creative Arts Team, 1981-1985 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Creative Arts Team, 1986-1993 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Sponsor Matters
  - Classified/Confidential Work at Universities, 1966-1970 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Classified/Confidential Work at Universities, 1978-1980 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Classified/Confidential Work at Universities, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Federal, Air Force Basic Agreement, 1960-1969 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Federal, Air Force Basic Agreement, 1970-1975 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Federal, Air Force Faculties Contract, Property Contract, 1961-1989 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Federal, Department of the Army, 1958-1967 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Federal, Department of the Navy Basic Agreement, 1969-1973 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Federal, Department of the Navy Basic Agreement, 1974-1986 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Federal, Department of the Navy Master Contract, 1961-1969 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Federal, DOD Critical Technologies Plan, Questionnaire, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Federal, DOD Strategic Defense Initiative, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Federal, Atomic Energy Commission Basic Agreement, 1960-1966 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Federal, Atomic Energy Commission Basic Agreement, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Federal, Atomic Energy Commission Basic Agreement, 1969-1972 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Federal, Atomic Energy Commission, Misc, 1970-1972 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Federal, Department of Energy Basic Agreement, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Federal, Department of Energy Basic Agreement, 1980-1987 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Federal, National Aeronautics and Space Administration, 1994-2000 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Federal, National Aeronautics and Space Administration, Renovation and Extension of Guggenheim School of Aeronautics, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - State/City, AdHoc Committee on Relations with New York City, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - State/City, Contracting with New York City, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - State/City, Contracting with New York City, Board of Education, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - State/City, Contracting with New York City, Board of Education, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - State/City, Contracting with New York City, Board of Education, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - State/City, Contracting with New York City, Board of Education, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - State/City, Contracting with New York City, Board of Education, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - State/City, Contracting with New York City, Board of Education, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - State/City, Contracting with New York City, Board of Education, 1989-1994 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - State/City, New York State/City Default Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - State/City, New York State/City Funding, 1988-1991 (Box 11, Folder 17)